<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>West Michigan R User Group</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>WestMichiganRUserGroup.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="WestMichiganRUserGroup.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 19:51:29 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 19:51:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Save the evening for userR&#39;s</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;meeting-overview&quot;&gt;Meeting Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;UseR’s, join us 6pm March 15 for pizza, networking and talk about R in Room 121E of DeVos Center. Same building as our inaugural meeting, but down the hall in a regular classroom. We have three presenters scheduled for the meeting. I’m also told we will have wifi access this time, so feel free to bring along your network devices so you can follow along with the discussions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;talk-formats&quot;&gt;Talk Formats&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;lightning-talks&quot;&gt;Lightning Talks&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lightning talks&lt;/em&gt; are short – 10 minutes with 5 minutes for questions – informal topic oriented talks, a couple of slides and/or a demonstration. Time to show off that great new package or code snippet you found (or developed yourself). Students, these are a great way to add to your resume! The format is essentially the same as conference contributed talks, but we’re a LOT less intimidating.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;use-case-talks&quot;&gt;Use Case Talks&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Use case&lt;/em&gt; talks are longer – 30 to 50 minutes – going into more depth and are more work flow oriented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;march-15-meeting-schedule&quot;&gt;March 15 Meeting Schedule&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;lightning-talk&quot;&gt;Lightning Talk&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dave Kendall (Advanced Radiology Services) - Word Clouds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;use-yase-talks&quot;&gt;Use Yase Talks&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Aaron Clark (Advanced Radiology Services) - My First Shiny App&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dave Zeitler (GVSU/FS) - RStudio Projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If anyone would like to give a lightning talk or a use case talk, please let Aaron or Dave know so we can schedule it. We may even be able to fit you into the next meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 08:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>WestMichiganRUserGroup.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/03/15/second-meeting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">WestMichiganRUserGroup.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/03/15/second-meeting.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Inaugural Meeting</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Join us to kick off the West Michigan R Users Group. We will be viewing recordings of the Rstudio Essentials programming webinars. Both new R programmers and experts should find useful hints both in the webinars and in the group discussions. Pizza will also be provided.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RStudio Programming&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Part 1: Writing code in RStudio&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Part 2: Debugging code in RStudio&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Part 3: Package writing in RStudio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note there is a parking permit for the Seward Ramp west of DeVos Center in our files section (under the ellipsis in the menu bar) as well as a map of the GVSU Pew Campus. We will be in room 107D of DeVos Center (#6D) on the map.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>WestMichiganRUserGroup.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/02/02/first-meeting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">WestMichiganRUserGroup.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/02/02/first-meeting.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
